A Guide to the Charles Olson Research Collection 1969.0001
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series V: Photographs
  - B. Photographs of Charles Olson
    - Charles Olson with Connie in Washington., Spring 1950. (Box 323:39b)
      Photograph by Marc Riboud. See Charles Olson Robert Creeley, v. 1, plate 2. Copy print only, courtesy of Jean Riboud.
    - Charles Olson standing in front of vine-covered barn., prior to 28 August 1950. (Box 323:40)
      - Charles Olson standing in front of vine-covered barn., August 28, 1950; 1 photographic print; 8 1/4 x 7 3/4 cm (Box 323:40)
        Photofinisher's date on the verso. Photo taken by Richard Wirtz Emerson on a view[?] to Washington, D.C. (copy enclosed to Creeley with a letter, September 24, 1950)
    - Charles Olson with Connie and infant Kate., 1951. (Box 323:41)
    - Charles Olson with infant Kate and Johanna Jalowetz at Black Mountain College, 1951.; 3 prints, 1 including Joanna Jalowetz. With 1 copy print. (Box 323:42)
    - Charles Olson at writing table (side view)., August 1951.; With copy print. (Box 323:43)
      Photograph by Jonathan Williams, Black Mountain. Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 5 page 63
      - Charles Olson at Bear Mountain, 1951; 1 photographic print; 19 x 19 1/4cm (Box 323:43)
        Photograph by Jonathan Williams. Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 5., Page 63.
    - Charles Olson at writing table (side view)., August 1951.; With copy print. (Box 323:44)
      Photograph by Jonathan Williams, Black Mountain.
    - Charles Olson at writing table (front view)., August 1951.; Copyprint only, courtesy of Jonathan Williams. (Box 323:45)
      Photograph by Jonathan Williams, Black Mountain. Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Olson 6 page 76
    - Charles Olson wearing serape., ca. 1953.; Copy print only, courtesy of Jonathan Williams. (Box 323:46)
      Photograph by Jonathan Williams, Black Mountain. See Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives Number 8 (Fall 1977): 65.
    - Charles Olson wearing serape., ca. 1953.; Copy print only, courtesy of Jonathan Williams. (Box 323:47)
      - Charles Olson wearing a serape., ca. 1953; 1 copy print (mounted); 20 1/4 x 25 1/4 cm
        Photograph by Jonathan Williams. Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 8. Page 65.
    - Charles Olson wearing serape. Closer view., ca. 1953.; Copy print only, courtesy of Jonathan Williams. (Box 323:48)
    - Charles Olson with Constance Olson (his head resting in her lap)., ca. 1953.; Copy print only, courtesy of Jonathan Williams. (Box 323:49)
      Photograph by Jonathan Williams, Black Mountain. See Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 8 (Fall 1977): 64.
      - Charles Olson with Constance Olson, his head resting on her lap., 1953; 1 copy print (mounted). 20 1/4 x 25 1/4
        Photograph by Jonathan Williams. Olson: The Charles Olson Archives, Number 8. Page 64
    - Charles Olson in a suit., ca. 1953.; Copy print only, courtesy of Jonathan Williams. (Box 323:50)
    - Charles Olson with daughter Kate., ca. 1953.; Copy print only, courtesy of Jonathan Williams. (Box 323:51)
    - Charles Olson with David Weinrib and Karen Barnes, Black Mountain., ca. 1953. (Box 323:52)
      - Karen and David Weinrib, Black Mountain, 1 photographic print; 9 1/2 x 10 3/4 cm (Box 323:52)
    - Photographs by Mary Ann Fretz, Black Mountain., Summer 1953. (Box 323:53)
      Contact sheet of snapshots, including Charles Olson and Kate on porch, Wesley Huss, David Tudor, Michael Rumaker, and others. Includes several enlarged copy prints. Gift to the Archives from Mary Ann Fretz Guisti.
      - Pianist David Tudor and M.L. Richards, Black Mountain College. Summer 1953. Photo by Mary Ann Fretz Giusti, Courtesy of Literary Archives, University of Connecticut Library, 1 photographic print; 10 x 12 1/2 cm (Box 323:53)
      - Michael Rumaker in study, Black Mountain, Summer 1953; 1 contact sheet, 2 prints; 12 x 6 1/2 cm (Box 323:53)
      - Poet Charles Olson with Daughter on the Dining Porch, Black Mountain College, Summer 1953. Photo by Marry ann Fretz Giusti, Courtesy of Library Archives, University of Connecticut Library, 1 photographic print; 16 1/2 x 15 1/2 cm (Box 323:53)
    - Group portrait of Black Mountain community, with Charles Olson, Betty Kaiser, Joe Fiore, Ebbe Borregaard, Ann Simone, Wesley Huss, Eric Weinberger, Dan Rice, and others., ca. 1956-1957. (Box 323:54)
      Filed with copy print and identifications by Michael Rumaker (1991). For a variant print with identifications, see The Arts at Black Mountain, p. 241.
      - Community gathering to announce the closing of the college. Front (left to right): Eric Weinberger, Dan Rice, Basil King, Betty Olson, Charles Olson, Harvey Fauenglass, Joseph Fiore, Ebbe Borregaard. Back: Wesley Huss, unidentified man, Eloise Mixon, Don Mixon, Ann Simone, Robert Hawley, unidentified woman., September 27, 1956; 1 photographic print; 6 1/2 x 3/4 (Box 323:54)
        Photo courtesy Dita Frauenglass Adam and Harvey Frauenglass
    - Charles Olson in San Francisco., 1957.; 3 sheets of contact strips and 1 enlargement, by Harry Redl, showing Charles Olson at a party and in posed portraits.With 3 copy prints. (Box 323:55)
      See A Guide to the Maximus Poems, plate 10.
    - Charles Olson in San Francisco, 1957 (Box 323:56)
      Photographed by Harry Redl.
      - Olson, in 1957, by Harry Redl., 1 photographic print (mounted); 23 1/2 x 17 1/2cm (Box 323:56)
    - Charles Olson in San Francisco, 1957; includes copies and 35 mm negatives (Box 323:57)
    - Charles Olson in a recording studio, probably in San Francisco., ca. 1957.; 1 sheet of 35mm-contact strips. (Box 323:58)
    - Charles Olson at Black Mountain., April 1957. (Box 323:59)
      Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 2 (Fall 1974): 58.
    - Charles Olson with Marion Wernick, November 1959. (Box 324:60)
      - How I look these days... (Charles Olson's Handwriting), 1 photographic print; 9x9cm (Box 324:60)
    - "Grants Receiving.", ca. 1961.; With 2 copy prints. (Box 324:61)
      See Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 9 (Spring 1978): page 73.
      - 'Grants Receiving', 1961; 1 photographic print; 10 1/2 x 8 1/4 cm (Box 324:61)
        Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 9. Page 73
    - Charles Olson contemplating a madonna., ca. 1961.; With 2 copy prints. (Box 324:62)
      See Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 9 (Spring 1978): page 72.
      - Charles Olson contemplating a madonna., 1961; 1 photographic print; 10 1/2 cm x 8 1/4 cm (Box 324:62)
        Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 9. Page 72.
    - 2 color prints., 1961 ca. September. (Box 324:62a)
      - Charles Olson inside a house smoking., September 3, 1960; 1 photographic print (color); 8 3/4 x 8 3/4 cm (Box 324:62a)
    - Charles Olson at home in Gloucester, sitting on table., ca. 1962.; With 2 copy prints. (Box 324:63)
      See Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 9 (Spring 1978): page 74.
    - Portrait. Color print., September 1962. (Box 324:64)
      - Charles Olson, Gloucester, photograph by Ken Irby, September 1962; 1 photographic print, color; 12 1/2 x 17 1/2 cm (Box 324:64)
    - Black and White Portrait., ca. 1963.; Polaroid original with 1 copy print. (Box 324:64a)
      See Call Him Ishmael, plate 3.
    - Charles Olson at Buffalo, with Warren Tallman, Allen Ginsberg, et al., 1963.; Copy Prints Only (Box 324:65)
      Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 4 (Fall 1975): pages 36-39.
      - Charles Olson at Buffalo with Warren Tallman, Allen Ginsberg, Jack Clark, Mrs. Rodefer, Pauline Wah, Olson and John Wieners. Photograph by Karen Tallman., 1963; 1 photographic print; 25 1/4 x 20 1/2 cm (Box 324:65)
      - Charles Olson, in Buffalo, with Ginsberg at Tallman's house. Photograph by Karen Tallman., Summer 1963; 1 copy print; 25 1/4 x 20 1/2 cm (Box 324:65)
        Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 4. Page 39.
      - Charles Olson, in Buffalo. Photograph by Karen Tallman., 1963; 1 copy print; 25 1/4 x 20 1/2 cm (Box 324:65)
    - Charles Olson at Buffalo, with Warren Tallman, Allen Ginsberg, et al. Photograph by Karen Tallman., 1963 (Box 325:66)
    - In kitchen with Betty., June 1963.; 3 prints, 1 early enlargement, 4 copy prints. (Box 324:67)
    - In kitchen with Betty., ca. June 1963.; With 3 copy prints (1 dated July 1968 by the photofinisher). (Box 324:68)
      - Charles Olson, 1963; 1 photographic print; 13 x 8 3/4 (Box 324:68)
    - Charles Olson in Gloucester., June 1963.; 2 prints. (Box 324:69)
    - Portrait by Elsa Dorfman, with her stamp. Verso of print heavily annotated by CO., ca. 1965. (Box 324:70)
      See Elsa's Housebook, p. 41 (a different photograph).
      - Annotation by Charles Olson [hard to read], 1965; 1 photographic print; 17 1/2 x 12 1/2cm (Box 324:70)
    - Charles Olson at Spoleto with Morse[?], ca. July 1965.; 2 prints. (Box 324:71)
      Photographs by M.L. Morse.
    - Charles Olson with Ezra Pound at Spoleto., July 1965.; 2 copy prints only. (Box 324:72)
      See A Guide to the Maximus Poems, plate 8.
    - Charles Olson onstage at Spoleto., ca. June 26, 1965. (Box 324:73)
    - Charles Olson and George Butterick walking in Gloucester., ca. 1968. (Box 324:74)
    - Portrait by Ann Charters. See Olson/Melville, frontispiece., 1968. (Box 324:75)
    - Charles Olson in Gloucester., 29 (Box 324:76)
      Photographs by Charles Stein. Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 1 (Spring 1974): pages 8-16. 6 prints and copyprints. Note: Some original prints are missing.
      - Charles Olson in Gloucester, 1969; 1 photographic print; 8 3/4 x 12 1/2 cm (Box 324:76)
        Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 1. Page 14
    - Charles Olson in Gloucester (Box 324:77)
    - Charles Olson in Gloucester (Box 324:78)
    - Charles Olson beckoning from house at Fort Square, and Charles Olson with N. Stewart Brown and Nick Ceppi., July 19, 1969; 2 color prints with 2 black-and-white copyprints. (Box 324:79)
    - Undated portraits, snapshots, and negatives, ca. 1937-1969. (Box 324:80)
    - Undated portraits, snapshots, and negatives (Box 324:81)
    - Charles Olson talking to a woman in a work-place (Box 324:82)
      - Charles Olson talking to Bernarda Shahn, Roosevelt N.J., n.d.; 1 photographic print; 17 1/4 x 23 1/4 (Box 324:82)
    - Undated portraits, snapshots, and negatives (Box 324:83)
      - The wedding of Jean Riboud or Krishna Ray at the Kellory estate, Silvermine Connecticut. Olson was a "bear man", October 1, 1949 (Box 324:83)
    - Undated portraits, snapshots, and negatives (Box 324:84)
    - Undated portraits, snapshots, and negatives (Box 324:85)
    - Charles Olson smoking a cigarette in Buffalo N.Y., April 1965 (Box 324:86)
      - Charles Olson smoking a cigarette in Buffalo, N.Y., April 1965; 1 photographic print; 25 x 20 cm (Box 324:86)
    - Undated portraits, snapshot, and negatives (Box 324:87)
    - Charles Olson in a classroom (Box 324:88)
      - Black and white picture of Charles Olson, lecturing, teaching. Annotated on the back. In David Ray's class, Cornell University, 23 July 1962, July 23, 1962; 1 photographic print; 25 x 16 cm (Box 324:88)
        Photograph by Lenny Lipton
      - Charles Olson in a classroom, among students. California Hall, Berkeley, July 20/23, 1965; 1 photographic print; 16 3/4 x 12 3/4 (Box 324:88)
    - Portrait of Charles Olson with a bird on his head, Enniscorthy 1946, includes 2 copy prints. (Box 324:89)
      - Portrait of Charles Olson with a bird on his head. Enniscorthy 1946, 1 photographic print; 13 3/4 x 8 1/4 cm (Box 324:89)
    - Charles Olson with a bird on his head, a woman feeding the bird. Enniscorthy, 1946, 2 copy prints. (Box 325:90)
      - Charles Olson with a bird on his head, a woman feeding the bird. Enniscorthy, 1946, 2 copy prints; 25 x 20 1/2 cm
    - Undated portraits, snapshots, and negatives (Box 325:91)
    - Undated portraits, snapshots, and negatives (Box 325:92)
    - Undated portraits, snapshots, and negatives (Box 325:93)
  - C. Charles Olson's Family
    - Charles Olson, Sr. Wearing hat, seated on rocks at seaside., ca. 1934. (Box 325:94)
      See The Post Office, plate 1.
    - Charles Olson, Sr. in the Worcester Continentals., undated (Box 325:94a)
      See Charles Olson Robert Creeley, v. 8, plate 6.
    - Charles Olson, Sr., various dates. (Box 325:95)
    - Charles Olson, Sr. (Box 325:96)
    - Charles Olson, Sr. (Box 325:97)
    - Mary T. Olson., various dates.; 9 prints. (Box 325:98)
    - Constance Wilcock Olson with Hilda Morley at Black Mountain College., undated (Box 325:99)
      - Constance Wilcock Olson with Hilda Morley at Black Mountain College., 1 photographic print; 9 x 6 1/4 cm (Box 325:99)
      - Robert Payne, Gerald Silvera, and unidentified woman on Monterella college, Alabama., 1950
        See also F134 and 135
    - Constance Wilcock Olson with infant Kate. Color print., 1952. (Box 325:99a)
    - Constance Wilcock Olson., ca. 1953. (Box 325:100)
      Photograph by Jonathan Williams. Copy print only.
    - Betty Kaiser Olson., ca. 1942-1968. (Box 325:101)
      - Summer 1943. Taken in New Paltz, N.Y. at Mrs. Celuch's home where we spent a week, 1 photographic print; 7 x 11 1/2 (Box 325:101)
      - Junior Dance, went with Richard Young, December 4, 1942; 1 photographic print; 10 x 13cm (Box 325:101)
    - Betty Kaiser Olson. (Box 325:102)
    - Kate Olson., n.d. (Box 325:103)
    - Betty Kaiser Olson. (Box 325:104)
    - Betty Kaiser Olson. (Box 325:105)
    - Kate Olson., ca. 1953. (Box 325:106)
    - Kate Olson., various dates.; 24 prints. (Box 325:107)
    - Charles Peter Olson., various dates.; 28 prints. Also includes miscellaneous negatives. (Box 325:108-109)
    - Vandla Olson Hedges., undated (Box 326:110)
      2 portraits, one published in A Guide to the Maximus Poems, plate 4. Copy prints only. Gift to the Archives from Philip Hedges.
      - Vandla Olson Hedges, Courtesy of Phillip E. Hedges, Topsham, M.E., Original taken in ... probably before her marriage, 1 photographic print; 17 x 11 1/2 cm (Box 326:110)
      - Vandla Olson Hedges, Courtesy of Philip E. Hedges, Topsham, M.E. Original taken in St. John, N.B. ... therefore after her marriage ..., 1 photographic print; 16 1/2 x 11 1/2 cm (Box 326:110)
    - "Aunt Augusta"., undated; 5 prints mounted. (Box 326:111)
    - Mounted prints of unidentified family members (in frame bearing a Gloucester frame-maker's label)., undated (Box OS)
  - D. Friends and Associates
    - Classmates., Before 1936. (Box 326:112)
      - Your Friend Sowell Field, 1928; 1 photographic print (mounted); 13 x 9 cm (Box 326:112)
    - Classmates, before 1936 (Box 326:113)
    - Classmates, before 1936 (Box 326:113a)
    - Classmates, before 1936 (Box 326:113b)
    - Paul Blackburn., Summer 1951. (Box 326:113d)
      - "Blackburn, summer 1951, Metropolitan Life Buildings fading away behind the firmness of cheekbone jawline, etc. Taken by self, very bad, focus, etc. Flattering, etc. Without glasses."--verso., 1 photographic print; 8 1/2 x 9 cm (Box 326:113d)
    - Classmates, before 1936 (Box 326:113c)
    - Robert Creeley. Includes photographs of Ann Creeley and sons., various dates. (Box 326:114)
      See Charles Olson Robert Creeley, v. 1, plate 1; v. 2, plates 2-4; v. 5, plate 6; v. 7, plates 4-5.
      - Robert Creeley and son David (right) with neighbor, August 1950; 1 photographic print; 8 3/4 x 12 1/2 cm
      - Creeleys, New Hampshire. O Pioneers!, 1950; 1 photographic print; 9 x 13 3/4cm (Box 326:114)
      - Creeleys, n.d.; 1 photographic print; 8 3/4 x 8 1/2 cm (Box 326:114)
      - Ann Creeley, 1951; 1 photographic print; 7 x 10 1/2 cm (Box 326:114)
      - Creeleys, 1951; 1 photographic print; 7 x 10 1/2 cm (Box 326:114)
      - Bobbie Creeley [?], n.d.; 1 photographic print; 7 x 10 cm (Box 326:114)
      - Creeley, n.d.; 1 photographic print; 7 x 10 1/2 cm (Box 326:114)
    - Robert Creeley. Includes photographs of Ann Creeley and sons., various dates (Box 326:115)
      - Robert Creeley. Banalbufar, Mallorca, 1952; 1 photographic print; 8 1/2 x 8 1/2 cm (Box 326:115)
        See also Jonathan Williams photo in Vincent Katz, Black Mountain College: Experiment in Art, page 272
      - Sept 1, 1950; Creeley, September 1, 1950; 1 photographic print; 10 1/2 x 7 cm (Box 326:115)
      - Creeley- N. Hampshire, n.d.; 1 photographic print; 8 3/4 x 8 3/4 cm (Box 326:115)
    - Robert Creeley. Includes photographs of Ann Creeley and sons., various dates; Copy prints (Box 326:116)
    - Fielding Dawson., undated (Box 326:116a)
    - Barbara Denny., undated; prints with 1 original negative. (Box 326:117)
    - Ed Dorn with son., March 1960. (Box 326:117a)
      - "That's Paul (Ed Dorn)", 1960; 1 photographic print; 8 3/4 x 8 3/4 cm (Box 326:117a)
      - Helene Dorn, 1960; 1 photographic print; 10 1/2 x 8 1/4 cm
    - Robert Duncan., ca. 1960. (Box 326:117b)
    - Vincent Ferrini., August 16-22, 1951; 7 prints. (Box 326:118)
    - "Vincent Ferrini ... and Mary Shore,", undated; newspaper clipping (Box 326:118a)
      See A Guide to the Maximus Poems, plate 12. 2 copy prints.
    - Tom Field. Polaroid print of wife and infant child. Cf. note to Charles Olson 1964 ca. July 23. (Box 326:118b)
    - Rainer Gerhardt. Includes family. 6 prints with 1 copy print. See Charles Olson Robert Creeley, v. 7, plate 3., Summer 1957, other dates. (Box 327:119)
      - Gerhardt, n.d.; 1 photographic print; 8 1/2 x 8 1/2 cm (Box 327:119)
      - Gerhardt family summer 1951; freiberg, Charles cordially, 1 photographic print; 6 1/4 x 9 cm (Box 327:119)
        See George Butterick, Co & RC Complete Commandence, Volume 7 after page 160
      - Rainer and Rendte [?] Gerhardt, 1 photographic print; 8 1/2 x 8 1/2 cm (Box 327:119)
      - Gerhardt Children [?], n.d.; 1 photographic print; 8 1/2 x 8 1/2 cm (Box 327:119)
      - Gerhardt[?], n.d.; 1 photographic print; 8 1/2 x 8 1/2 xm (Box 327:119)
      - Gerhardt, n.d.; 1 photographic print; 8 1/2 x 8 1/2 cm (Box 327:119)
    - Hettie Jones nursing infant daughter. "The 2 Lady Joneses"--verso., undated (Box 327:119a)
      - "The 2 Lady Joneses", n.d.; 1 photographic print; 12 1/2 x 9 cm (Box 327:119a)
    - Rene Laubies., undated (Box 327:119b)
      - Rene Laubies, friend of Creeley, 1 photographic print; 8 1/2 x 8 1/2 cm (Box 327:119b)
    - Kenneth Rexroth with daughter., undated; 2 prints (Box 327:120)
      - Rexroth and daughter, 1 photographic print; 8 3/4 x 9 cm (Box 327:120)
      - Rexroth's daughter, n.d.; 1 photographic print; 8 3/4 x 9 cm (Box 327:120)
    - Michael Rumaker., undated (Box 327:120a)
    - Helen Stein., undated; Gift to the Archives of Mary Shore. With 2 copy prints. (Box 327:121)
      - Helen Stein- Painter. Gloucester Mass. Given to me by her brother in Boston..., 1 photographic print; 17 1/2 x 12 1/2 cm (Box 327:121)
    - Gael Turnbull., undated; 3 prints. (Box 327:122)
      - Gael Turnbull and Wife, 1 photographic print; 11 x 7 cm (Box 327:122)
    - Jonathan Williams holding Jargon edition of Maximus., undated (Box 327:123)
    - Diana Woelffer., undated (Box 327:123a)
    - Emerson Woelffer in studio. Photograph by Diana Woelffer.v, 27 December 1951. (Box OS1)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. Includes pictures of Charles Peter Olson and Harry Martin. (Box 327:124)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. Includes pictures of Allen Ginsberg, Robert Creeley, Panna Grady, and Michael Rumaker (Box 327:125)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. (Box 327:126)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. (Box 327:127)
      - Albert Sorrantino, n.d.; 1 photographic print (mounted); 23 1/2 x 18 cm (Box 327:127)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. (Box 327:128)
      - "Miami"--verso. A woman on the beach, n.d. (Box 327:128)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. (Box 327:129)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. Includes pictures of T.S. Eliot and Stefan Volpe (Box 327:130)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. (Box 327:131)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. Icludes pictures of Kate Olson (Box 327:132)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. (Box 327:133)
      - Suzie Hare, Coggeshill, Wiscasset, Maine, 1952; 1 photographic print; 8 1/4 x 8 1/4 cm
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. (Box 327:134)
    - Unidentified photographs of people. Includes pictures of Edward Dorn's children (Box 327:135)
      - To aunt Betty, with love, Lionel Josguise. In this picture he is eight months old, he is going to be a year old this month., n.d.; 1 photographic print (mounted); 18 1/2 x 15 1/4 cm
    - Unidentified photographs of people. May include members of Olson's family. (Box 328:136)
  - E. Black Mountain College
    - The Studies Building at Black Mountain College reflected in Lake Eden, reproduced from a college catalog., ca. 1950.; 2 copy prints (Box 328:137)
      Olson: The Journal of the Charles Olson Archives, Number 2 (Fall 1974): pages 60-61.
    - "T.J.," handyman at BMC. Contact print with enlarged copy print., ca. 1953. (Box 328:138)
      - T.J.- handyman at BMC, 1953; 1 photographic print; 6x6cm (Box 328:138)
    - "From my house Black Mt (when it was the Jalowitz's) looking to the farm. Olson, October 23rd 1968"--verso., ca. 1953 (Box 328:139)
      - "From my house Black Mt (when it was the Jalowitz's) looking to the farm. Olson, October 23rd 1968"--verso., ca. 1953; 1 photographic print; 17 x 21 cm (Box 328:139)
    - Photographs taken at the site of Black Mountain College, then Camp Rochmont, by Frank Ballard., Summer 1977.; 51 prints. Gift to the Archives from Frank Ballard. (Box 328:139a-c)
  - F. Gloucester
    - Shipyards: David Story yard and John Bishop yard, undated; two prints, presentation inscriptions to Charles Olson dated 1960. With Charles Olson's annotations. (Box 328:140)
      - John Bishop's Yard...[?], 1 photographic print; 12 1/2 x 17 1/2 cm (Box 328:140)
      - David Story yard..[?], 1 photographic print; 12 1/2 x 17 1/2 cm (Box 328:140)
    - Unidentified Gloucester shipyard (mounted 19th-century print), undated (Box OS)
    - Photographs of Gloucester paintings., undated; minor annotations by Charles Olson. (Box 328:141)
      - Miss Adel wrote...[?] (Charles Olson annotation), 1 photographic print; 10 x 12 1/2 cm (Box 328:141)
      - This is shipyard ... [?], 1 photographic print; 10 x 12 1/2 cm (Box 328:141)
    - Photographs of Gloucester paintings., undated (Box 328:142)
    - Photographs of Gloucester ships., undated; 3 prints. (Box 328:142a, OS4)
      - Destroyer Flusser[?] stationed at Gloucester ... during the celebration., n.d.; 1 photographic print; 13 x 25 1/2 cm (Box 328:142a)
    - 19th-century portraits of Gloucester residents., undated; 18 cartes-des-visites and 1 cabinet photograph. (Box 328:143)
      - To Dearest Alice on her umptieth unbirthday. From Humpty D. Question: Did an anty miss even live in the Hunters House?, 1 photographic print; 14 1/2 x 9 cm (Box 328:143)
    - Portrait of Homer Barrett, Gloucester., undated (Box 328:144)
    - 19th-century scenes., undated; 2 prints and 1 stereocard. (Box 328:145)
    - 19-Century Scenes., n.d. (Bin 329:146)
    - 19-Century Scenes, n.d. (Box 329:146a)